Angel Robert Paule



+639923723538 angelrobertpaule28@gmail.com

Objective

Information technology college graduate with three years of work experience in a variety of technical fields who is highly motivated and technically proficient. Looking for a challenging position in a fast-paced company where I can use my knowledge and abilities to help develop and implement new IT solutions. While producing outstanding results and assisting in the expansion and success of the company, I seek to further my expertise.

Experience

- Analytica Business Solutions Inc. / Junior Back-End Software Engineer
 Collaborate with the development team to understand project requirements and
 translate them into well-structured and efficient back-end solutions. Design, develop,
 test, and maintain server-side components using appropriate programming languages
 and frameworks
- Sutherland Global Services / Customer Service Representative
 Serve as the first point of contact for customers seeking
 technical assistance via phone
- Triseed Software Inc / Junior Software Engineer

 Collaborate with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality software solutions.

05/12/2022-28/09/2023

03/02/2021-25/09/2022

27/09/2023-15/11/2024

Education

• Lauc Pao Elementary School
Elementary

• Sta. Cruz Academy

Junior High School

15/04/2016

• STI College Of San Fernando Senior High School 05/05/2018

• Don Honorio Ventura State University

Bachelor Of Science In Information Technology

15/09/2022

Skills

- Programming(Java, Php(Native and Laravel), Javascript, Typescript, Node.js, Python)
- Computer Skills(Microsoft Office)
- Verbal and written communication

Personal Details

• Date of Birth : 28/05/2000

• Marital Status : Single

Apolit Paul

Angel Robert Paule